Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative Files, 1972-1987
  - D, 1972-1979 (Box 300)
  - Da-Do, 1976-1987 (Box 300)
  - Danielson's Group, undated; (4 folders) (Box 300)
  - Delpha Internationl Group, undated (Box 300)
  - Delta Sigma Fraternity, 1980 (Box 300)
  - Derge, David R., 1971-1979 (Box 300)
  - Diamant, Steven, 1973 (Box 300)
  - Distinguished Ranks, 1978-1980 (Box 300)
  - Dp-Dz, 1974-1980 (Box 300)
  - E (Box 300)
    - 1974 (Box 300)
    - 1974-1984 (Box 300)
  - Earlham College, 1976 (Box 300)
  - Elks Lodge, 1973 (Box 300)
  - Elliott, Michael, 1981 (Box 300)
  - Enrollment, 1978 (Box 300)
  - Equal Opportunity, 1974 (Box 300)
  - Eschbach, Judge Jesse E., 1980 (Box 300)
  - Evans, David and Rae, 1980 (Box 300)
  - External Activities that Produce Compensation, 1985-1986 (Box 300)
  - F, 1971 (Box 300)
  - Fa-Fl, 1975-1980 (Box 300)
  - Faculty Research Fund, 1973-1980 (Box 300)
  - Fancher, John E., 1986 (Box 300)
  - Faris, Gene, 1982 (Box 300)
  - Farrell, John, 1978-1983 (Box 300)
  - Fenske, David E., 1980 (Box 300)
  - Fine Arts Museum, 1976-1978 (Box 300)
  - Fineberg, Milton J., 1979-1981 (Box 300)
  - Fisher, Jack C., 1977-1983 (Box 300)
  - Fleming, Gordon, 1976 (Box 300)
  - Floyd, Ralph, 1978 (Box 300)
  - Fo-Fz (Box 300)
  - Football Hall of Fame, 1981 (Box 300)
  - Indiana University Foundation (Box 300)
    - General, 1978-1985; (2 folders) (Box 300)
    - Aircraft, undated (Box 300)
    - Board of Trustees-IU Foundation, 1979 (Box 300)
    - Director-Search and Screen, 1987-1988 (Box 300)
    - Executive Committee, undated (Box 300)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 300)
    - Materials, 1979 (Box 300)
    - Priorities Coordination Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 300)
    - Program Development Fund, 1969-1971 (Box 300)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1976 (Box 300)
  - Fraenkel, Peter, 1977-1985 (Box 300)
  - Franklin, J.A. Jr., 1979 (Box 300)
  - Friedman, Thomas A., 1981 (Box 300)
  - Friends of Art, 1978 (Box 300)
  - Friends of Music, 1978-1988 (Box 300)
  - Fund Drive Preparation, 1979 (Box 300)
  - Funds for Education, 1972 (Box 300)
  - G, 1973 (Box 300)
  - Ga-Gl, 1979-1983 (Box 300)
  - Gaetke, Elmer-Eshter, 1981 (Box 300)
  - Gamble, Gary, 1973-1978 (Box 300)
  - Gatson, Lavarrel, undated (Box 300)
  - General and Technical Studies (Division of) – Bonser Report, 1978-1979 (Box 300)
  - Georgia (University of) System Members meeting, 1984 (Box 300)
  - Georgia Institute of Technology, 1980 (Box 300)
  - Giusti, Joseph, 1979 (Box 300)
  - Go-Gz, 1974-1983 (Box 300)
  - Goerke, Glenn, 1981 (Box 300)
  - Gonso, Harry, 1980-1986 (Box 300)
  - Gray, Carl M., 1978-1983 (Box 300)
  - Greece Trip, 1976 (Box 300)
  - Green, Jim, 1980-1982 (Box 300)
  - Gros Louis, Kenneth, 1984 (Box 300)
  - Gutman, Caroline and Phil, 1976-1987 (Box 300)
  - Ha-Hl, 1973-1987 (Box 300)
  - Hallagan, George R. II, 1977-1980 (Box 301)
  - Hamm, George, 1975-1980 (Box 301)
  - Hamm, Gregory, 1980 (Box 301)
  - Hamm, Michael, 1973 (Box 301)
  - Hansen, President Arthur G., 1974-1982 (Box 301)
  - Harmony School, 1986-1988 (Box 301)
  - Harrell, C., 1981-1986 (Box 301)
  - Harvey, William, 1971-1987 (Box 301)
  - Hauck, Everett J., 1984-1985 (Box 301)
  - Hayes, Brice E. and Wanda, 1979 (Box 301)
  - Heller, H. Frederick, 1980 (Box 301)
  - Hesbergh, Theodore, 1975-1986 (Box 301)
  - Higher Education Commission, 1973-1980 (Box 301)
  - Ho-Hz, 1980-1987 (Box 301)
  - Holiday Bowl, 1979 (Box 301)
  - Holmberg-Wright, Kristin, 1983-1986 (Box 301)
  - Hook, August, 1975 (Box 301)
  - Hoosier Society of Florida, 1984-1985 (Box 301)
  - Hopcraft, David, 1980 (Box 301)
  - Horrigan, Fred, 1975-1987 (Box 301)
  - Houx, Jolee, 1978-1980 (Box 301)
  - Hudnut, William H., 1974-1980 (Box 301)
  - Hungarian Academy of Sciences, 1981 (Box 301)
  - Hungary, 1981 (Box 301)
  - "Hunting" Trips, 1975 (Box 301)
  - Hyneman Endowment Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 301)
  - I, 1978-1987 (Box 301)
  - I Men's Association, 1986-1989 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Academy, 1981-1986 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Academy of the Social Sciences, 1986 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Central University, 1980 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Construction Group, 1979-1982 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Economic Development Council, 1987 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Office for Campus Ministries (IOCM), 1980-1986 (Box 301)
  - Indianapolis Corporate Community Council, 1984 (Box 301)
  - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1981 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Public University Presidents Conference, 1978 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Society – New York, 1978 (Box 301)
  - Indiana State Data Center, 1978 (Box 301)
  - Indiana State Police Alliance, 1984 (Box 301)
  - Indiana State University-Evansville, 1970 (Box 301)
  - Indiana Training and Development, 1978 (Box 301)
  - Indiana University Hall of Fame, 1982 (Box 301)
  - Indiana University Press - China Publication, undated (Box 301)
  - Indiana Vocational Technical College (Ivy Tech), 1974-1978 (Box 301)
  - Intercollegiate Conference of Faculty Representatives, 1981 (Box 301)
  - Interfraternity Luncheon, 1987 (Box 301)
  - International Council of the Future, 1981 (Box 301)
  - International Platform Association, 1985 (Box 301)
  - Inter-University center of Post Graduate Studies, 1981 (Box 301)
  - Investors Trust Assurance Company (Box 301)
    - General, 1982-1985; (6 folders) (Box 301)
    - General, 1982-1985; (3 folders) (Box 302)
  - Irish Correspondence, undated (Box 302)
  - Irwin, Dr. Gleen-Marianne, 1978 (Box 302)
  - J, 1976-1985; (2 folders) (Box 302)
  - James, Jim, 1977 (Box 302)
  - Jelavich, Barbara and Charles, 1980 (Box 302)
  - Jesseph, Dr. John E., 1974-1981 (Box 302)
  - Jones, Edward, 1978 (Box 302)
  - Jones, Frank and Jerri, 1980-1988 (Box 302)
  - Jordan References, 1982 (Box 302)
  - K, 1974-1976 (Box 302)
  - Ka-Kj, 1974-1983 (Box 302)
  - Kappa Sigma Alpha-Epsilon, 1986 (Box 302)
  - Kariuki, Lucy Murugi, 1980 (Box 302)
  - Karnjanaprakorn, Choop – Bangkok, Thailand, 1971-1981 (Box 302)
  - Kelley, Wilma, 1974 (Box 302)
  - Kentucky Colonels, 1972-1984 (Box 302)
  - Kigin, Thomas, 1973-1987 (Box 302)
  - Kinsman Publishing Co., 1981 (Box 302)
  - Kintner, Ambassador William, 1974-1977 (Box 302)
  - Kirkwood, Walter B., 1979 (Box 302)
  - Kittle's Furniture, 1973 (Box 302)
  - Kl-Kz, 1974-1986 (Box 302)
  - Knight, Bob, 1975-1981; (3 folders) (Box 302)
  - Kramer, David W. (Box 302)
  - Kreig, William, 1972-1976 (Box 302)
  - L, 1975-1987; (2 folders) (Box 302)
  - Landini, Richard G., 1973-1977 (Box 302)
  - Law School (Box 302)
    - General, 1974-1987 (Box 302)
    - Committee I, 1975 (Box 302)
    - Committee II, 1974 (Box 302)
  - Legislators, 1980 (Box 302)
  - Likins, Edgar, 1978 (Box 302)
  - Lilly Endowment, 1974-1978 (Box 302)
  - Lilly Inventory, 1977 (Box 302)
  - Long, Benjamin, 1974-1975 (Box 302)
  - Long Range Plans (Box 302)
    (See Box 302a)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 302)
    - 1974-1984 (Box 302)
  - Lugar, Senator Richard, 1977-1980 (Box 302)
  - Luther, Donna, 1980 (Box 302)
  - M, 1973-1975 (Box 302)
  - Ma-Ml, 1973-1982 (Box 302)
  - Mallory, William G., 1984 (Box 302)
  - March of Dimes Celebrity Roast, 1980 (Box 302)
  - Massachusetts Commissioner of Education, 1986 (Box 302)
  - Mathenge, 1978-1983 (Box 302)
  - Mc, 1974-1983 (Box 302)
  - McCloskey, Mayor Frank, 1972 (Box 302)
  - Medical School Dean, 1983 (Box 302)
  - Menke, Robert, 1978 (Box 302)
  - Merritt, Lynn, 1974-1980; (2 folders) (Box 302)
  - Michigan, University of, 1979 (Box 302)
  - Mission Statements, 1977-1987 (Box 302)
  - Mobley, Tony, 1976 (Box 302)
  - Morris, James T., 1982 (Box 302)
  - Mulholland, Jack, 1980 (Box 302)
  - N, 1974-1981; (2 folders) (Box 302)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), 1983-1987; (3 folders) (Box 302)
  - National Center for Higher Education, 1975 (Box 302)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), undated (Box 302)
  - National Football Foundation Hall of Fame, 1979 (Box 302)
  - Nering, Theodore D, III, 1980 (Box 302)
  - Newman Foundation, 1973-1989 (Box 302)
  - Norvell, Lee, 1980-1982 (Box 302)
  - O, 1974-1987 (Box 302)
  - Oakland City College, 1981 (Box 302)
  - Olson, Gerald, 1986 (Box 302)
  - O'Neil, Robert-President of University of Wisconsin, 1981 (Box 302)
  - Orescanin, Dan, 1973-1979 (Box 302)
  - Organization (IU) Materials, 1972-1974; (5 folders) (Box 302)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1973 (Box 302)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1973 (Box 302)
  - Orescanin, Dan, 1975 (Box 302)
  - P, 1973-1987 (Box 303)
  - Pacific (University of), 1987 (Box 303)
  - Pagenkopf, W.H., 1974-1976 (Box 303)
  - Palmer, Judith, 1985 (Box 303)
  - Parrish, Mike (SPEA Librarian), 1984 (Box 303)
  - Pastorial Letter, 1985 (Box 303)
  - Pease, Ed, 1973-1975 (Box 303)
  - Personnel Division, 1983 (Box 303)
  - Peterson, Dwight, 1976-1986 (Box 303)
  - Piguet,Fr. Leo-NICM material in general, 1979 (Box 303)
  - Pinnell, George, 1977-1980 (Box 303)
  - Plager, Sheldon, 1975-1980 (Box 303)
  - Planning, 1976 (Box 303)
  - Political Science, 1987 (Box 303)
  - Pope John Paul II, 1979 (Box 303)
  - Pozzatti, Rudy, 1977 (Box 303)
  - Pro Program, 1978-1979 (Box 303)
  - Public Broadcasting-Anneberg Grant, 1981 (Box 303)
  - Public Relations Office, 1976 (Box 303)
  - Purdue Ag Fish Fry, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 303)
  - Presidency, Center for Study, 1978 (Box 303)
  - President's Office – Reorganization Suggestions, 1981 (Box 303)
  - Presidential Review, (3 folders) (Box 303)
  - Presidential Search Committees, 1968 (Box 303)
  - Presidential Search, 1985-1987 (Box 303)
  - Q, 1975-1980 (Box 303)
  - R, 1977-1980 (Box 303)
  - Ra-Rl, 1973-1974 (Box 303)
  - Radio Basketball/Football Contract, 1966-1981 (Box 303)
  - Real Estate Holdings IU, 1981 (Box 303)
  - Real Estate Indianapolis, undated (Box 303)
  - Reclassification Project, 1983 (Box 303)
  - Red Mass Dinner, 1980 (Box 303)
  - Regional Campuses (Box 303)
    - Realignment, 1973-1980; (3 folders) (Box 303)
    - East (Richmond), 1978 (Box 303)
    - Fort Wayne, 1979; (3 folders) (Box 303)
    - Indianapolis (Box 303)
      - Faculty Club, 1975 (Box 303)
      - Law School – Search and Screen Committee for Law School Dean, 1978-1981; (3 folders) (Box 303)
      - Report, 1979-1985 (Box 303)
      - Search and Screen, Vice-President, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 303)
    - Kokomo (Box 303)
      - General, 1979 (Box 303)
      - Faculty Senate, 1978 (Box 303)
    - Northwest (Box 303)
      - Chancellor McNeil, 1974 (Box 303)
      - Foundation, undated (Box 303)
    - South Bend (Box 303)
      - General (Box 303)
        - 1974-1980 (Box 303)
        - 1981 (Box 303)
      - Fund Raising, 1977 (Box 303)
      - Leon Rand, 1985 (Box 303)
  - Regional Health Secinece and Vocational Programs, undated (Box 303)
  - Reorganization, 1968-1974; (3 folders) (Box 303)
  - Reorganization, 1968-1974; (2 folders) (Box 304)
  - Research and Graduate Development Dean Candidates, 1976; (2 folders) (Box 304)
  - Retirement Committee, 1977 (Box 304)
  - Review Procedures-For University Administration, 1984 (Box 304)
  - Review of Existing Programs, 1978 (Box 304)
  - Rich, Claude, 1975 (Box 304)
  - Richardson, Jeff, 1981 (Box 304)
  - Ro, 1975-1989 (Box 304)
  - Roberson, Tim, 1974 (Box 304)
  - Roehr, Eleanor, 1971-1982 (Box 304)
  - Rogers, Ralph, 1975-1980 (Box 304)
  - Rotary Club (Box 304)
    - General, 1969-1980 (Box 304)
    - Award Survey, 1978 (Box 304)
  - Ryan, John M., 1984-1987 (Box 304)
  - Ryan, John W. (Box 304)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1986; (4 folders) (Box 304)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1968-1993 (Box 304)
    - Foreign Visa Info, 1970-1980 (Box 304)
    - Fraternities, 1973-1975 (Box 304)
    - Honorary Degree Citations (Box 304)
      - General, 1977-1984 (Box 304)
      - Notre Dame, 1978 (Box 304)
    - Investiture, 1975 (Box 304)
    - Notes, undated (Box 304)
    - Pettit / Fuller, 1980 (Box 304)
    - NCAA, Executive Director Search, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - Presidential Review, 1978-1979 (Box 304)
    - Retirement, 1987 (Box 304)
    - School of Public and Environmental Affairs (SPEA) (Box 304)
      - Appointment, 1981-1987 (Box 304)
      - Office Suite, undated; (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - Speech Kit, 1981 (Box 304)
    - Speech Materials, 1980 (Box 304)
    - Travel (Box 304)
      - SEA-Rome-London trip, 1973 (Box 304)
      - Foreign Travel Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 304)
      - Asian/U.S Educators Conference-Manila, August 1975; (3 folders) (Box 304)
      - International Association of Universities - Moscow Conference, August 1975; (2 folders) (Box 304)
      - Asian/U.S Educators Conference-Japan, July 1976; (2 folders) (Box 304)
      - Warsaw University, September 1976 (Box 305)
      - Ireland Tour, June 1977 (Box 305)
      - Israel – Yugoslavia, June 1977; (5 folders) (Box 305)
      - Taipei, Taiwan – China, October 1977 (Box 305)
      - Yugoslav Seminar, Baltimore Maryland, June 1978; (2 folders) (Box 305)
      - Seminar of the European Universities-Warsaw, Poland, June 1978 (Box 305)
      - People-to-People delegation to China, July - August 1978 (Box 305)
      - Alumni Trip to China, October – November 1978 (Box 305)
      - China Trip, February 1979; (3 folders) (Box 305)
      - Hungarian-German Trip (AAU), June 1979 (Box 305)
      - Egyptian Trip, August 1979 (Box 305)
      - Manila, April 1980 (Box 305)
      - Yugoslav Conference, June 1980 (Box 305)
      - Trip to Kenya, June 1980 (Box 305)
      - Official visit to Malawi, June 1980 (Box 305)
      - University of Mexico Seminar, September 1980 (Box 305)
      - Satellite Info for Hamburg, June 1981 (Box 305)
      - Munich, Zurich, June 1981 (Box 305)
      - Hungary Trip, August 1981 (Box 305)
      - Trip to Yugoslavia and Bulgaria, January 1982 (Box 306)
      - Salzburg Rectors' Conference, March 1982; (2 folders) (Box 306)
      - Trip to Zurich, April 1982 (Box 306)
      - University Telecommunications Consortium for International Exchange-Munich, April 1983 (Box 306)
      - Bulgarian Delegation at Lilly House, May 1983 (Box 306)
      - Hungary, June 1983 (Box 306)
      - German-American Meeting, July 1983 (Box 306)
      - Birmingham, England, August 1983 (Box 306)
      - 19th Anniversary of IUC Dubrovnik, September 1983 (Box 306)
      - Saudi Trip, November 1983 (Box 306)
      - Trip to Berlin and Hamburg, West Germany, December 1983 (Box 306)
      - IUC Dubrovnik Executive Committee, Wroxton England, 1984 (Box 306)
      - Taiwan Trip, June 1986 (Box 306)
      - International Urban Universities Conference, September 1986 (Box 306)
      - London, October 1986 (Box 306)
      - University of Louisville, Board of Overseers, November 1986 (Box 306)
      - Fulbright 40th Anniversary and Conference in Kuwait, April 1987 (Box 306)
      - Warsaw, Poland, May 1987 (Box 306)
      - UCLA Commencement (Recipeint of the UCLA Medal), June 14, 1987 (Box 306)
      - Malaysia, etc., July 1987 (Box 306)
      - China Visit, July 1987 (Box 306)
      - SUNY: Opening Celebration Moscow State University, August 2001 (Box 306)
    - Who's Who, 1979-1987; (8 folders) (Box 306)
  - S, 1974-1980 (Box 306)
  - Sa-Se, 1973-1983 (Box 306)
  - St. Joseph's College, 1983 (Box 306)
  - St. Thomas Aquinas Center Purdue, 1978 (Box 306)
  - Salaries, 1979 (Box 306)
  - Sample, Glenn, 1976-1977 (Box 306)
  - San Pietro, 1980-1981 (Box 306)
  - Schellhammer, James, 1980 (Box 306)
  - Schrader, Edward A., 1973-1978 (Box 306)
  - Sebeok, Thomas, 1977 (Box 306)
  - Sh-Si, 1973-1984 (Box 306)
  - Shane, Harold, 1978-1986 (Box 306)
  - Sheraton Hotels, 1978-1981; (2 folders) (Box 306)
  - Sigma Chi Fraternity, 1987 (Box 306)
  - Simon and Associates, 1985 (Box 306)
  - Six Presidents, 1980 (Box 306)
  - Sj-So, 1973-1983 (Box 306)
  - Sliger Recognition Dinner, 1987 (Box 306)
  - Smith, D. Richard, 1971 (Box 306)
  - Social Science History Association, undated (Box 306)
  - Society for Advanced Studies, 1986 (Box 306)
  - Sp-Sz, 1976-1981 (Box 306)
  - Special Investigation Team, 1975-1976 (Box 307)
  - Special Projects: Courtyards, Speeches, Entertainment, 1986 (Box 307)
  - Spencer and Spencer, 1981 (Box 307)
  - Staff Merit Awards Presentation, 1986 (Box 307)
  - The Stafford, undated (Box 307)
  - Stanford University, 1976 (Box 307)
  - Stein, Jules, 1978-1979 (Box 307)
  - Stimming, Chas, 1975-1987 (Box 307)
  - Stoner, Richard, 1980-1984; (3 folders) (Box 307)
  - Straub, Terrence, 1979-1980 (Box 307)
  - Strauss, Jerome M., 1980 (Box 307)
  - Students, 1977-1978; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Students (Foreign)--Lists, 1978 (Box 307)
  - Student Fees, 1977 (Box 307)
  - Sycamore Valley Gun Club, 1979-1986 (Box 307)
  - Sutton Unveiling Ceremony, 1972 (Box 307)
  - Sweeney Memorial Scholarship Fund Project, 1973 (Box 307)
  - T, 1974-1985; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Tarzian, Sarkes, 1977-1987 (Box 307)
  - Templeton, George, 1975-1980 (Box 307)
  - Tenri University, 1976 (Box 307)
  - The University of Texas, 1985 (Box 307)
  - Thailand (Box 307)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 307)
    - Project Photos, 1955 (Box 307)
      REMOVED
  - Theatre Circle, 1983 (Box 307)
  - Theological Education Fund, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Thomas, Ladd, 1975 (Box 307)
  - Thompson, Dr. Hugh, 1975-1984 (Box 307)
  - Threatening (Policy Concerning the Receipt of), 1984 (Box 307)
  - Tierney, Jim, 1976-1977 (Box 307)
  - Trustees, 1975-1981; (3 folders) (Box 307)
  - U, 1978-1984; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Ullman, Harrison, 1979-1982 (Box 307)
  - Union Bank and Trust Company, 1973 (Box 307)
  - University Advisory Council-ACLI, 1978 (Box 307)
  - University Club-Boston, 1980 (Box 307)
  - University Club Recognition of Pres. Ryan and Mrs. Ryan, 1987 (Box 307)
  - University Counsel, 1971-1983 (Box 307)
  - University Faculty Council Members, 1986 (Box 307)
  - University Relations (Box 307)
    - General, 1969-1983 (Box 307)
    - Review, 1980 (Box 307)
  - University of Utah, 1987 (Box 307)
  - Utah Symphony, 1981; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Utah State University, undated (Box 307)
  - V, 1975-1987 (Box 307)
  - Wa-Wh, 1974-1986 (Box 307)
  - Waiyaki, Mrs. Z.n., 1980 (Box 307)
  - Washington, D.C., 1975 (Box 307)
  - Weathersby, George B., 1976-1987 (Box 307)
  - Weil, Gotshal and Manges-WX and NYC, undated (Box 307)
  - Weimer, Arthur M., 1975-1979; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Weiss, William L., 1979-1987 (Box 307)
  - Well house Society, 1977-1987 (Box 307)
  - Wells, Herman B., 1972-1987 (Box 307)
  - Wells, W.D., 1973-1977 (Box 307)
  - Wentworth, Jack, 1983 (Box 307)
  - White Elephant (Thailand), 1987 (Box 307)
  - The White House, 1980 (Box 307)
  - White River Park Development Commission, 1979-1989 (Box 307)
  - Wi-Wz, 1975-1987 (Box 307)
  - John Baron/WIAN "live" interview, 1987 (Box 307)
  - Wilcox, Howard (Howdy), 1981-1983; (3 folders) (Box 307)
  - Wildwood Valley, 1974-1976 (Box 307)
  - Roy Wilkins Memorial Committee, 1984 (Box 307)
  - Williams, Camilla, 1982 (Box 307)
  - Williams, Edgar G., 1975 (Box 307)
  - Williams, Ernest E. (News-Sentinel), 1977-1979 (Box 307)
  - Wilson, George, 1978 (Box 307)
  - Wilson, (Jim) James L., 1981 (Box 307)
  - Windless Orchard, 1976 (Box 307)
  - Wisconsin (University of), 1985 (Box 307)
  - Wise, Charles, 1987 (Box 307)
  - Wit, Daniel, 1976 (Box 307)
  - Wolfson, Lester, 1979-1988; (3 folders) (Box 307)
  - Wood, Michael, 1980 (Box 307)
  - Woods, Michael E., 1978; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Woodburn House, undated (Box 307)
  - Wyche, Samuel D., 1983 (Box 307)
  - XYZ, 1978-1987; (2 folders) (Box 307)
  - Yeagley, Jerry, 1982 (Box 307)
  - Yugoslav Review, 1982 (Box 307)
  - Zhejiang University, undated (Box 307)
  - RESTRICTED FILES - Boxes 308-309 hold restricted files (Box 308)
  - H-Z (Box 309)